{
    "1": {"question": "What are your 3 primary colors and how do you get them?", "answer": "Red, yellow, blue - laws of color, default"},
    "2": {"question": "What are your 3 secondary colors and how do you get them?", "answer": "Orange, green, violet, mixing a primary color with the one next to it"},
    "3": {"question": "How do you get tertiary colors?", "answer": "Mixing a primary color with a secondary color beside it in equal amounts"},
    "4": {"question": "Blue and red mixed in even amounts create what color?", "answer": "Violet"},
    "5": {"question": "What factors contribute to the final outcome of the hair color?", "answer": "Hair texture, density, porosity, natural hair color, contributing pigment, and hair color product"},
    "6": {"question": "How many levels are in the level system?", "answer": "1-10"},
    "7": {"question": "What is another word for a client's natural color of hair?", "answer": "Hue"},
    "8": {"question": "What are the 4 types of hair color?", "answer": "Temporary, semi-permanent, demi-permanent, and permanent"},
    "9": {"question": "How many shampoos does it take to remove a temporary hair dye?", "answer": "One shampoo"},
    "10": {"question": "What is the main difference between a semi and demi permanent color?", "answer": "Semi's last about six to eight shampoos and are also used directly from the bottle because there is no mixing required. Demi-permanent hair colors use a developer"},
    "11": {"question": "What is an aniline derivative?", "answer": "Product found in all permanent hair color products that tell the particles to get big once inside the cortex"},
    "12": {"question": "What 2 products use a developer?", "answer": "Demi-permanent and permanent use a developer"},
    "13": {"question": "What is the range of the level system?", "answer": "Shows the light or darkness level of the hair ranging from 1-10. 1 on the level system is black and 10 is the lightest blonde"},
    "14": {"question": "What is the difference between a dye remover and a stain remover?", "answer": "Dye remover removes artificial pigments from the hair and a stain remover which is used when a color has spilled on a client's skin and you need to remove it."},
    "15": {"question": "List some of the ways you can apply highlights/lowlights?", "answer": "Ways to color are the cap, foil and freeform techniques."},
    "16": {"question": "What is the difference between highlights and lowlights?", "answer": "Highlights color lighter strands in overall dark hair. Lowlights put dark streaks in typically overall lighter hair"}
}

